When she was seventeen there wasn't a man she'd let near her. When
she was eighteen there wasn't one she'd keep away.
Claudelle Inglish is a drama film directed by Gordon Douglas.
A young daughter of poor farmers is forced by her mother to ditch her young boyfriend in order
to marry an old rich neighbor but the girl rebels by becoming the town's harlot.
Claudelle Inglish, played by Diane McBain.
Clyde Inglish, played by Arthur Kennedy.
Dennis Peasley, played by Will Hutchins.
Jessie Inglish, played by Constance Ford.
S.T. Crawford, played by Claude Akins.
Harley Peasley, played by Frank Overton.
Claudelle Inglish is a 1961 American film directed by Gordon
Douglas and based on the 1958 novel by Erskine Caldwell.
It stars Diane McBain and Arthur Kennedy.
It was nominated for an Academy Award in 1962 for
Best Costume Design (Howard Shoup).
The film was cast with many Warner Bros.
Television contract stars, including Diane McBain who replaced
the original choice for the lead Anne Francis.
McBain was then co-starring in Surfside 6 and had
previously appeared in Parrish.
The tone is emotional.